hitechos.com 2015-06-09

# Hi-Tech Outsourcing Services Privacy Statement

Protecting your privacy is important to Hi-Tech Outsourcing Services and its employees. We believe confidentiality and protection of customer information to be one of our most fundamental responsibilities.

Worldwide clientele to our credit with primary customer base in USA, Canada, UK, EU, Australia, Middle East and other countries. Our 7 offices across the globe including India, USA, and Scandinavia have a proven track record of providing BPO, Architectural Engineering Construction (AEC) services, engineering solutions, and software solutions to all our esteemed clients. 

### Personal information we collect:

Personal information is the data that is associated with your name or personal identity. The personal information you provide us may include name, e-mail address, phone numbers and project details.

Hi-Tech OS may use your personal information to understand your needs and interests better and to provide you with better services.

Hi-Tech OS does not sell, rent or lease any individual’s/company’s personal information or lists of email addresses to third parties for commercial and/or marketing purposes.

### Notification of Changes:

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website so that you will always be aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

### Web Servers:

Hi-Tech OS automatically receives and records information from your browser via our servers, including your IP address, the time and information regarding the page you requested, etc.

### Copyrights & Trademarks:

Hi-Tech OS ensures that the material on this website is accurate and current.

Hi-Tech OS has independently developed all the content presented on its website. The copyright for content provided by Hi-Tech OS will remain the property of Hi-Tech OS and the company does not allow its re-printing on any medium without a prior written permission.

Disclaimer: All the trademarks and all the logos are the property of their respective owners.
